<Document>

# Welcome to Project Atlas!
Glory to Nanotrasen

## What is Atlas Sector’s purpose?
Atlas sector is a sector specifically to study planets that all have an interesting feature to them that are uncommon amongst typical planet formations such as planets still capable of supporting life even in severely hostile conditions. These stations are also used as tourist attractions for the curious and studious.

## Server and Game Rules
This server is **MRP+**, or medium to high roleplay, with a minimum age requirement of **18+**

## Rule 1: Don’t be a dick!
You should already know how to be a decent enough person, but this also extends to in game interactions. You’re more likely to get banned than you think if you’re going to be a dick.

## Rule 2: ERP relations
This server is an 18+ server, in which Erotic Roleplay is allowed. This is to be treated as a privilege, and not a right. Any misusage of this privilege may lead to any consequence that admins see fit, such as role bans.

### Rule 2.a: Roles and ERP
EVERYONE is required to do their chosen job, and should not ignore or excuse their lack of effort with ERP. Just roleplay it out when you go back and check in and out for your job.

### Rule 2.b: CONSENT MATTERS!!
Consent obviously matters in an ERP allowed environment, in which the Atlas staff asks that you take precautions to not involve or offend anyone. This does include, however, demarcating spaces as openly sexual (such as leaving writing stating the bar has converted to a strip club.) ALL ERP REMAINS IN SUBTLE CHANNELS.

## Rule 3: Play more seriously!
This server is MRP+, we want to have more serious roleplay and character interaction/development. You can have goofy characters, but that doesn’t mean that you get to play a character with absolutely no common sense.

## Rule 4: No Discrimination in any form
This server is run by a queer person of color who’s autistic, and also their autistic boyfriend. Don’t. You will be banned with NO appeal if you’re caught showing any forms of discrimination towards marginalized groups of people.

### Rule 4.a: No in game specism!
No you don’t get to call the moth a made up slur either! That’s weird! Let’s not do that, maybe? Please?

## Rule 5: No Metas
No metagaming, powergaming, metafriending, or metacomming about important information.

Simple, you’re expected to play as if you are your character, who shouldn’t be 100% aware of what sword is a better weapon against security’s armor.

### Rule 5.a: Allowances
You MAY however, send current round screenshots of funny moments so long as they do not breach 2.b. You may also communicate with each other in VC about how the round is going, but MAY NOT abuse this privilege for metagaming or powergaming purposes.

### Rule 5.b: Grudge vs Metagrudge
In character, grudges are allowed! Metagrudges however, are clear acts meant to upset the player out of character, targeting that player’s other characters, and harassment out of character or extends beyond what would be reasonable in a regular negatively charged relation. You can fight each other in character, but if you go assaulting them as their other character, or clearly making unpleasant comments about their other characters in a way to upset them, this will be punished.

## Rule 6: No Spamming!
Both for the Discord server and in game, please refrain from spamming. Let’s be honest with ourselves here, Space Station 14’s community is highly neurodivergent, creating any form of noise disruption that could be uncomfortable by spam pinging, spamming messages at random, or, in the case of in the game, spamming any emotes that have additional sounds to them, is highly disrespectful and can cause physical pain to many players. Don’t do it please.

## Rule 7: Speak English
We don’t currently have the means to moderate in other languages other than Google translate, and we all know how unreliable that is, so for the ease of the moderation team please speak in English to the best of your ability.

## Rule 8: Respecting Others
“But didn’t rule 1 and 4 cover this?” Well sure, but more specifically don’t flame people in game, flame other forks of SS14, and remember to use things to mark specific topics or even tone that may not be easily conveyed through your word choices. We encourage the usage of tone tags and the spoiler tag, essentially.

### Rule 8.a: No Generative AI! 
The use of Generative Artificial Intelligence to produce Texts, Art, Images, is strictly prohibited. Reason being is that AI is a direct middle finger to all of the artists in the server. 

## Rule 9: No EORG!
What’s that mean? No end of round griefing! Our end of round is the evac shuttle docking to the station. Please avoid spacing, killing each other, or vandalising CC or the shuttle. Antags may attack on the evac shuttle as long as they avoid spacing it, but no more fighting in CC.

## What to expect when playing:

### Continuity!
You’re allowed to keep in character relations, this may include character grudges, romantic and platonic relationships, and even pets or etc. This however does NOT mean you can metagrudge, as that includes attacking the person out of character.

### Action!
Each station is designed to have specific challenges, the shifts might not ever get boring! Always a plus, right?

### Art!
Layzii here specifically, I do art! I love drawing, you might be featured in art relating to any shifts that I think are fun in a visual manner! You don’t even have to pay!!

### Fair Treatment!
Moderation and admins are subject to the exact same rules as you are, regular player! If you have a reason to be upset with specific moderators, I will personally talk to them. I don’t play about justice for all, you’ll be fine.

### Unique Scenarios!
Have you ever been on a server that so desperately could use an admeme? You like having an active project manager with an imagination that can only be contained through Pandora’s box? You’re in for a treat then!

### Brand New Content!
The project managers have worked hard to create new content, as well as searching for interesting content from other servers to respectfully pull the code for and modify to our heart’s content to fully create the kind of atmosphere we’re going for.

## I’ve been banned?
If you believe you’ve been banned unrightfully, the admin and moderation team will work diligently with you in the Discord server through a ban appeal. However if we found that this ban was applied correctly, you may just have to wait unless you can make a good case as for why you should be let back in.

Certain rule breaks are also weighted differently, let’s say you were banned for being a dick, which wouldn’t explicitly include being racist or ableist, it’s up to how the admin judges your actions, you might only get banned for like 3 hours. All bans are subject to varying lengths based on the judgement of our administration and moderation team, and of course as mentioned above you have a chance to report them if you feel targeted by them for any reason.

</Document>
